Hello,
We already printed some cards by your website. We are indeed developing a party game. We project to reprint 7 piles of 180 cards (with 28 small boxes). In addition, each pile goes with 4 boards. 
That reprinting is in the purpose to spread the game and check if it could interested some people and if we could sell a bigger quantity. In this case, we will reprint a lot of piles.
To begin, we remain if you can propose an all-in package containing 7 piles of 180 cards (bridge), 28 boards (26 centimeters/31 centimeters) and 28 boxes (for bridge cards).

Could you make us an offer ? 

+ expliquer jeu
+ dire qu'on a fait des tests
+ dire que c'est en français
+ kickstarter